{
  "data": [
    { "K": "一", "OY": "いち, いつ", "KY": "ひと", "M": "one", "MM": "" }
  ],
  "descriptions": {
    "K": "Kanji",
    "OY": "On'Yomi Reading" ,
    "KY": "Kun'Yomi Reading",
    "M": "Meaning",
    "MM": "Mnemonic"
  },
  "sets": [
    { "front": "K", "back": "OY", "hint": "MM" },
    { "front": "K", "back": "KY", "hint": "MM" },
    { "front": "K", "back": "M", "hint": "MM" },
    { "front": "OY", "back": "K", "hint": "MM" },
    { "front": "OY", "back": "M", "hint": "MM" },
    { "front": "KY", "back": "K", "hint": "MM" },
    { "front": "KY", "back": "M", "hint": "MM" },
    { "front": "M", "back": "K", "hint": "MM" },
    { "front": "M", "back": "OY", "hint": "MM" },
    { "front": "M", "back": "KY", "hint": "MM" },
  ]
}
